A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, DNA, Series G FA342
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Files for the 1968 Campaign, 2; 5.6 Cubic Feet
  - Statement on American Indian (Box 22, Folder 270)
    Includes material used in preparation of statement.
  - Statement on Women (Box 22, Folder 271)
    NAR statement on women sent to publications.
  - Stephens, Thomas (Box 22, Folder 272)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Stephens on issues.
  - Sughrue, Mary (Box 22, Folder 273)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Sughrue on issues.
  - Sughrue, Mary - Agriculture (Box 22, Folder 274)
    Specific material on agricultural issues.
  - Temporary Help (Box 22, Folder 275)
    Vouchers and bills for temporary employees.
  - Thank You Letters (Box 22, Folder 276)
    List of individuals to send thank you letters.
  - Turtle, Robert (Box 22, Folder 277)
    Notes from telephone conversation.
  - TV/Radio Transcripts (Box 22, Folder 278)
    Press releases of transcripts of NAR appearances.
  - "U.S. News and World Report" (Box 22, Folder 279)
    Copy of article on "Rockefeller Talks on the Issues."
  - Watts, William (Box 22, Folder 280)
- Files for Other Campaigns and Issues, 3; 3.6 Cubic Feet
  This subseries is a conglomerate of files created during Rockefeller's other campaigns. Rockefeller's run for the governorship in 1958 and his early plans for a presidential candidacy in 1960 are among the contents. There are also files pertaining to New York state and city politics, including an examination of the 1961 New York City mayoral campaign.
  - Campaign 1958 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    Selection of policy and position papers prepared for the gubernatorial campaign. General information and memoranda.
  - Campaign 1958 - Agriculture (Box 23, Folder 282)
    Selection of policy and position papers prepared for the gubernatorial campaign.
  - Campaign 1958 - Anti-Discrimination (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Campaign 1958 - Child Welfare (New York State) (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Campaign 1958 - Crime (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Campaign 1958 - Draft Position Papers (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Campaign 1958 - Economic Trends and Business (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Campaign 1958 - Education (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - Campaign 1958 - Health, Mental Health, and Health Insurance (Box 23, Folder 289)
  - Campaign 1958 - Judiciary and the Courts (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - Campaign 1958 - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 23, Folder 291)
  - Campaign 1958 - Labor Management (Box 23, Folder 292)
  - Campaign 1958 - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 293)
    Selection of policy and position papers prepared for the gubernatorial campaign. Papers on labor, local government, state finances, transportation, and special transportation problems in New York City.
  - Campaign 1958 - Public Welfare (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Campaign 1958 - Rehabilitation (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Campaign 1958 - Social Insurance (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Campaign 1958 - Summary Papers Notebook (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Campaign 1958 - Summary Sheets (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Campaign 1958 - Transportation (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Campaign 1958 - Transportation - Copy 2 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Campaign 1960 - Analysis (Box 25, Folder 301)
    Issue sheets, convention notes, position papers and information regarding the 1960 presidential campaign. Statistical analysis of election results in 1960 for New York State.
  - Campaign 1960 - General Information (Box 25, Folder 302)
    Issue sheets, convention notes, position papers and information regarding the 1960 presidential campaign.
  - Campaign 1960 - GOP Convention (Box 25, Folder 303)
    Issue sheets, convention notes, position papers and information regarding the 1960 presidential campaign. Press releases, speeches and remarks given during the convention.
  - Campaign 1960 - GOP Convention (Box 25, Folder 304)
  - Campaign 1960 - Issues, Domestic (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Campaign 1960 - Issues, Foreign (Box 25, Folder 306)
  - Campaign 1960 - Issues, Foreign (Box 25, Folder 307)
  - Campaign 1960 - Nixon Campaign (Box 26, Folder 308)
    Issue sheets, convention notes, position papers and information regarding the 1960 presidential campaign. Correspondence and memoranda on Nixon position and remarks on Rockefeller issues.
  - Campaign 1960 - Platform Comparisons (Box 26, Folder 309)
    Issue sheets, convention notes, position papers and information regarding the 1960 presidential campaign. Report on differences and similarities between the Republican and Democratic platforms.
  - Campaign 1960 - Political Survey, New York State (Box 26, Folder 310)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers (A-D) (Box 26, Folder 311)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers (E-L) (Box 26, Folder 312)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers (E-L) (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers (M) (Box 27, Folder 314)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers (M) (Box 27, Folder 315)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, the Campaign (Box 27, Folder 316)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, Domestic (Box 27, Folder 317)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, Domestic (Box 27, Folder 318)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, Domestic Summaries (Box 27, Folder 319)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, Foreign (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Campaign 1960 - Position Papers, Foreign Summaries (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Campaign 1960 - Statements by Others (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Campaign 1960 - Statements by Others (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Campaign 1960 - Statements by Others (Box 28, Folder 324)
  - Campaign 1961 (Box 29, Folder 325)
    Files, political survey on the New York City Mayoralty Race.
  - Campaign 1961 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Campaign 1961 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Campaign 1961 (Box 29, Folder 328)
  - Issues 1961 - Civil Defense, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 329)
    Issue summaries and statements by others on a variety of issues.
  - Issues 1961 - Civil Defense, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 330)
  - Issues 1961 - Report on Governor's Program, June 1961 (Box 30, Folder 331)
    Issue summaries and statements by others on a variety of issues. Poll of New York State reaction to Rockefeller's New York efforts.
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Economic (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Economic (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Government, Education, Medical Aid (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Government, Education, Medical Aid (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Latin America (Box 30, Folder 336)
  - Issues 1961 - Statements by Others, Latin America (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - Issues 1962 - Arms Control and Disarmament (Box 31, Folder 338)
    Position papers, issue summaries, and statements by others on domestic and foreign issues.
  - Issues 1962 - Berlin (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - Issues 1962 - Budget and Fiscal Policy (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Issues 1962 - Civil Defense (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Issues 1962 - Eighty-seventh Congress and the Kennedy Legislative Program (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Issues 1962 - Federal-State Relations (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - Issues 1962 - Foreign Aid (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Issues 1962 - Iran (Box 31, Folder 345)
  - Issues 1962 - Laos (Box 31, Folder 346)
  - Issues 1962 - NATO (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Issues 1962 - Position Papers to be Used With the New York State Congressional Delegation (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Issues 1962 - South Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Issues 1962 - Statements by Others (Box 31, Folder 350)